hello everyone this is Richard with
hydrogen technology today calm you are
looking at my latest sell the purpose of
this video is just to show you guys what
this cell does with just plain old tap
water so real quick just about the cell
there's 17 plates they are wired and
spaced about 164 they're wired basically
starting at the bottom here it's a
positive neutral negative neutral
positive so on and so forth there's a
neutral between each negative there's a
total of four negatives here let's go
fill this full of tap water I'm going to
try to do this without breaking the
breaking need the action at all so you
guys can see what I see walking through
my house here there's the bathroom at
the cell cool water
just going to fit a little bit over the
cell so turn this back off here for
water walk back in here try to keep this
shortfall you youtubers already there we
go it's going to look a positive pick up
the negative and here we go she's on
the side shot seemed out with you better
than let's blow it out a little bit I've
actually measured that at five aunts
that little bit you see there in this
configuration equates to around 5 ounces
a minute not very much so the next video
I'm going to add a little bit of
hydrogen oh excuse me a little bit of
sodium hydroxides this is a lowes blend
of it it's basically drain opener but
what you need to look for is that right
there one hundred percent lie and on the
back you'll read you know somewhere in
here sodium hydroxide one hundred
percent sodium hydroxide okay oh there
you go pure tap water about about 5
ounces 67 ounces a minute
continue on to the next video we'll add
a little sodium hydroxide and see what
we guessed